If you know the ingredients, then
you can guess about the dishes. Wow, we want to
live like we have fun, and the world does
n't want to live like we have fun.
Answer five marks in MCQ on
Make Some Noise. Jai Vasavada
[Appreciation]
Useful Ball for the amazing Jai Vasavada. Thank you, thank you, love you all, love you
Rajkot and love you, love you, love you,
what's the special thanks, sir,
from us, to stay in Rajkot. So,
we got the guests and set up. All of us.
And our first trip was like this. All the
fare was saved.
And we had one main problem. We used to
call all the guests in Rajkot. But
after no one picked up the phone, we found out that we were calling in the evening.
We used to call in the afternoon.
In this, it was like this: I grew up in Gondal, was
born in Bhavnagar, now I live in Rajkot. So, there is
a shed in Rajkot too.
Rajkot is the center of the entire Saurashtra.
And from there, the water of the rivers in the entire Saurashtra flows into the confluence.
And so people from all over Saurashtra
come to Rajkot as a confluence.
What is the truth?
Sir, why is this confluence six hours
away from Vadodara? The telephone line goes so far while reaching it. I wonder
how far it is. I watched the night before that Rajkot had arrived. Then I
saw that OPPO board. I
said, "It has arrived now." Brother,
now you come from Vadodara. So, the Rajkot
airport board comes first. Then a bridge
that is never completed. Now no one is working
there. If someone does work there, it will be completed. It is
exactly like the one that is half a bridge near Kuwarwa and is
lying like a remnant. It seems like aliens have
built it and left it there.
And then Rajkot is here. And then Rajkot
city is ours. It is like the fringes of the fringes. And
I like the fringes of the fringes very much.
Yes, it is like the
fringes of the fringes. Everything in between is like a
circle, starting from the racecourse. You
can see it in a big circle. I took a
satellite view from above.
And then the whole  A man's hand is the
reason why the handle comes out like this, Amin, it keeps
pulling me till the end, the handle keeps
pulling me, keeps pulling me, we do
n't have to work hard, I know so much in this time,
now it's like this, I do the same work that you
do, I also do loveri, I have
reached the point of writing, I don't know how to speak or write, I have been able to do it, we can
make a career of loveri, Gujaratis, it's
because loveri is embedded in us,
but sir, you said love you loveri, but you have
n't watched a single episode of loveri yet,
yes, that's why I have seen you all,
yes, that's why it's like this, if
you
know the ingredients, then
you can guess about the recipes,
I'll answer you right away, sir, we
say, no need to work hard today, if
this comes out, it's great, 20
Jaibhai, as many reels as he speaks, as many times as he will make
.
But sir, I follow your social media very
closely and I have seen that
you are very active on social media and
you also undertake many campaigns within it.  There are
also many conflicts with some people,
some of your photographs are very beautiful,
mine are not so beautiful, but the ones I
post are of beauties and
mostly they are like that. If you survey the whole world, if you
count the life expectancy of India, it is
around 65 to 70, so from that, let's
cut off the first
year and wait like that. First, you spend
half of your energy as you get younger. Whether someone
calls you or not, it ends in that.
Then when someone calls you,
you turn 25 and then we
start running away from the person who calls you or if no one calls you anymore,
that period of 55-60 starts and then in the
relationship, then the one above you calls you, that journey
begins. In between, the years of life
that we call actual life are said to be 30
to 40 years. You
can pull it off. When you keep your mood colorful, you can keep it at
30-40 and a few.  You can extend it,
but the point is this, when we have lived for so many years,
we want to have fun and
not live like the world has fun,
sir, this is just a problem for my father, please
explain this to my father, and once I
said,
brother, seeing your skills, sir, we asked about social media
uploads, direct, thousands of
years, we asked what you like,
how do rivers flow, and
I have not read as many books as you have
written, sir, I
like it, but the original question you asked, the
root of it is that there should be happiness,
now what you see gives you joy, and a
person who is happy, first of all, does not commit crimes, does not get angry,
secondly, does not get angry, so
this is social service, to be happy and to be happy,
you people must do these four
social services, to make
people happy, a
person who is happy does not commit murder, a person who is happy does
not rob anyone, if you forgive me,
all these things are for fun, brother,
I  It seems that brother, beauty is also a
subject of fun. I post good poems. If
I get to read a good poem at two in the morning, I
post it at two in the morning.
People's attention goes to the poems. Okay,
but if they don't go into these poems, the poems are
dangerous. Wherever there are obstacles on the road,
there are bolts.
Even the Indian Army kills them. If you go to Kashmir, then okay. Brother, there are
curves ahead and all the curves are dangerous.
So be careful with a caution.
Jaybhai, I asked you, "What do you drink when you
come here?" Like, "
Where is this energy? Where is this energy coming from?" There was a
picture of you. Yes, if I have
permission to drink, then I have everything. Because I
travel all over the world, I get to drink for free.
But I don't drink anything that
those people drink. I definitely drink this blood. I
write and speak like this,
keep some attitude, and don't be a slave to anyone in life.
But I always say
that brother, what should we drink that will make us sober and
what should we do after we are sober? What should we do to have fun? The next day, we will not remember anything.
So, if we drink petrol, we should drink that
which will not make us sober. If
petrol does
not make us sober and catches fire, then the
memories will become seeds inside.
Oh yes, but there is something in it that in order to
drink petrol, you need an engine. The
engine should have torque. For that, it
needs four wheels. Now, instead of four wheels, God gave us
two hands, two legs, a nose and
a brain on our head. So what to
drink and what not to drink is decided.
Think about it. I have
received the answer for so long.
Why are you sitting quietly? I don't have anything to
say because I have come from here and
I have to go
home with only knowledge. We had arranged a session for free at home. I had told you
earlier, chant Bapbo
Pari, if he comes, then I will enter the chopper like Baba.  If
we did, we would have opened an ashram. If
you say so, then it is true that
I have to speak and benefit everyone by doing this.
Sir, and answer five marks in MCQ.
[Appreciation]
What is the matter,
brothers, I swear, you are a great man,
Sir, a real big fan, what do
you need, water, breath, etc. In the
midst of which you have spoken so much,
we will take a little more from you today, that this is my rap, rap, God, this is it,
but we have this business and we have money to
speak and write, so all this comes.
This is a watch generation, how can we get it without it? How can we get a
pair of shoes, how can we get it without it? We
hope that it will
come to you, but it will come because you
people deserve it. And I must also say that
our Rajkot is colorful, so only these
fun-loving people live here. If
someone does not fight with each other, then by
stopping the fight,  He asks back that if you
say something, then it will be fun to build something
[appreciation]
Hey man, I feel like I have a
dial-up connection of 256 kbps right now. This man is
driving away the excitement on AGPS. He is
finishing his PhD after having his meals every day. Brother, you have
amazing knowledge and amazing philosophical talks. It is
said to be amazing. But sir, when I was reading about you, the
knowledge you have now, the
philosophical talks you are doing, it is very deep
rooted. But then I read that
when you were doing schooling in Gondal,
you did home schooling for many years, so
how did you get the facility of bunk bed after that?
Because you can't go back home after bunking from home.
I often say that brother, some
people say that brother, even though he is at the end of the earth, he has
such difficulty in finding the end of the house that he keeps leaving home and going to the
earth.
This is what we all do now.  Of the
great men we see, half of them are those
who were
upset at home and then went out and became so
set that they
even gave advice on how to run other people's houses. The
point is that
my parents made the decision to homeschool me, which made me very happy
because our house was
not a school but a home. People say that home school was not schooling at all.
Their only job was to
put different things in front of us
according to their age, so as they grew older, they
also changed them. That was their vision at that time.
Today, they are not in either world, but what
I am doing today is very important.
Their contribution is very big. That was their vision at that time. They
started with children's stories.
They used to make me happy, saying, "Brother,
who are you, how about hitting the bunk?" or "Let's hit the bunk a
little." The word school means a place to
gather and have fun in Greek. "Skola" means a place to gather and have fun.
I was a little bit more for comedy.
I have no other purpose, no, I have to keep
saying this in between,
but you ask a good question, maybe it will be useful for everyone
who is watching, when they are watching, that
we give so much burden to the children by sending them to school
that they lose their fun,
people are sleeping in bunks to have fun,
even if they leave home, they go to the Himalayas
for that, they go to beer bars
for that, then
you get fun from stories, when you get fun from the
toys around you, your
parents become your toys
because they had so much time that no
one has today, we pay high fees in school because we don't have time, there are
schools where we are ready to pay 15 lakh rupees in exchange for that time, my parents had
time,
so they went to Fero. I said, we were a
middle class family, we didn't have money, we didn't have a
mobile phone, we didn't have internet, there weren't
so many channels on TV, we used to
go to the neighborhood to watch German on TV  People also
changed during that era, I still
say today that who would find it useful?
Suppose there was an age when there were Jivram Joshi and
Ramanlal Soni, Galbo Shiyal and Mia Fuski,
Adukiyao Dhadukiya,
that age when Harish Nayak, Yashwant Mehta, all our
children's writers, Ratni Vyas, Bulbul, the toy was shining.
From there, they changed gears.
Indrajal Comics came,
Walt Disney and all those comics came
and took all that and then upgraded the cinema,
so the screen also came, the film fair
also came. But
I completely relate to you
because I also have a nine-year-old daughter. The
burden you are talking about. Today's schools have become
such that if you give 15 lakhs, give 25 lakhs to
send her to school, then there is a burden on the child, but there is also a
burden on the parents. The assignment that has to be done is
just yesterday, my daughter,
what is the spelling of phosphorus?
Simple last FORSTV VY
this home schooling did not do this where does he know B
that is why I asked you to write it down that is if so
I say the following that he will write it will be a
mistake when negative marking comes he will
know that okay then the teacher will write below
what is the correct spelling with red pen then he will
learn from it and then he will teach you B
dad if the correct spelling is this
I know exactly PHO RO PARS
nice
but sir my one question is that you go to
eat somewhere and a waiter asks you like
yes sir what would you like to have
and you then ask what do you have there that
we have Chinese Italian
and then you answer there like normal or
hey Chinese Italian what to eat Gujarati
food the fun thing is that take eggplant with potatoes
there such a long there teach B or
then order food and eat it first of all it is like that the
language of conversation with waiters in Gujarat is Hindi  There is no Gujarati or
English in Gujarati.
Go to any corner of the world,
start with the waiter in Hindi
and especially in Gujarat,
even if you go to Chotila, start talking in Hindi. If you
go to Vadodara, start talking in Hindi.
If Amitabh goes, let's go to Canada and do the same.
I have many friends or we go abroad. You have all
gone and here too there will be many friends. There will be a
place for us. So, any host will say, "
Today, I will feed you khichdi." I will say, "
My aunt's cooking is good. I
eat at home. I eat good khichdi. I
eat good rotis. You feed me good khichdi here.
What kind of khichdi are you feeding me? Come here and
land right away. You must be missing your homeland.
I said, "It's been 16 hours now. It's been a
month. Now,
you don't miss home food." I said, "
I don't miss my home, I don't miss my
parents." I want a good
burger for free.  Remind them and feed them
and they also feed you the food in such a way that you get the
taste of home, the real taste of home, but they have
spices that are local and some of them are
imported and some are expired. Do you
know that
some people don't get some types of flour, some
types do
n't have that taste at all?
Yes, they do.
Everything comes frozen. And when samosas are
fried, half of them come fried and the other
half you order, they fry
them. So it's like this: the taste comes here and the taste doesn't come there because here we have the sweat of the cook and all that, and there the dirt of the people's hands and everything gets mixed and then a taste comes out. The truth is, if they are making chutney, they have
n't even seen the vessel in which the chutney is made for four
years. So what's the matter with their hands? What's the matter? I got
acidity after hearing this
and you can't freeze all this stuff.
[Appreciation]
and all this sweat.  It
seems
that you have to run Maharaj on a treadmill all
day long. There is a plate placed below in which sweat is
collected. Fill it in a deep-lock bag and then
freeze it in the freezer. Then,
two spoons of sweat from this water of Panipuri are
now dehydrated. Do you know
that
people from here dehydrate whatever Ghughra they have, that is, they
remove all the moisture from it and
go there and add water to it. As it is,
sir, what other line could have come in this? The water
there is not the same as the water here.
We have to take it from the river.
But we are all as watery as
most of the people who came from Kathiawad.
Wherever you go, there is no shortage of water.
So not all of us have that much water. If you
show us how to drink, then so much water comes into your
mouth. They are
watery people. You have a jalsa, put
water in it. If I told you, it does
n't matter how much change there is. Show us the water.
Debt is the strength of Gujaratis. Let
anyone in the world show us
what has happened to us. We used to come and
show us water.
But sir, you have drunk water from the Ghat Ghat. You have
traveled all over the world. Right, which
country is there where Gujaratis are absolutely
Gujaratis? You think that the Gujaratis here
are the same as the Gujaratis.
Yes, this is an interesting question.  There are
Gujaratis from Africa, and many mature Gujaratis who
moved from Africa to the UK remained just as
mature.  You see, we still don't speak,
and we use words like "Vayadhi" a lot, "
Vayadhi" apadhi, we do
n't even use such words in our language.  My mind felt like a needle, that's why
I saw that the first to
leave Africa were Gujaratis, the NRIs who
went to Africa, the
tradition of Gujaratis did
not start directly from America, so
what is it in America? Everyone has become very rich
and the value of the dollar has increased a lot and all that Think
Big and Make America Great Again and
superpowers and all that nonsense and all the
aliens come there, they come there, no other city is
visible, if Thanos looks from above, he does
n't see Delhi, he doesn't see Tokyo, he directly
comes to Rajkot, he sees a spaceship and goes away, or
some land happened once, someone spits out a mole, the
male function has
not been done. If there is such a
plot in my mind, no one makes a
film, if the budget is big, then no one,
our Gujarati producers, dare not do it
because they don't do anything other than the budget,
that's the only thing that matters, the budget is the movies,
so there
is such a plot in my mind that an alien spaceship
comes to India and then such a mess in the lifestyle of India.  They get lost in
this
hustle and bustle, the noise of the local train and everything in between, and
then finally they all get
tired of India and say, "Oh, we can't survive in this one country, so
how are we going to conquer the world?"
Sir, magic has come. If a
guest comes to the bedroom, how does the incense put in that wheat
sack taste like
wheat?
That flying saucer comes here.
Someone from our village in Gujarat comes and
sits in this. All those people have some kind of a trap.
If Lalo fills my tea
bag in this,
brother, climb on it and make two or four reels.
People climb on buffaloes and make reels.
I have seen it with my own eyes,
but while leaving, sir, anything. You have to tell the
people of Rajkot, the Gujaratis, through the medium of love,
oh, I enjoy it a lot. All I
want to say is, do love, tear your heart out, but in
this way.  Where there is a meeting of love, where there is a
meeting of friends, we do it
there. Where there is a
wrong judgment on someone, whether
you should wear such clothes or not, whether you should
listen to such songs or not, whether you should speak
or not, it is
their own choice. If you don't
like it, ignore it. Ignore it. Ignorance is a
very big weapon.
Exactly. Fighting is not a big weapon. Opposition is
not a big weapon because in it, the
person in front of you grows bigger. As you oppose,
his size increases. His publicity increases. Ignore it.
Ignore it if you feel like it and have a concert.
We have come to this earth to perform concerts and if you
can do so much service without getting in the way of someone's concert, then it is a very big thing.
You don't do any other service, but don't bother anyone. That is the
biggest social service.
What is the matter,
sir? Please make my father understand. I
feel that I am too old to have a meeting with these fathers.  It's over
that all the
dads are sitting together and
talking about girls right now, Teeji, the dad came straight away, the
whole thing is
yes, sir, if the other men get a
reply from B Riyasen, it will be amazing, Jai
Vasavadh was Jai sir, thank you, thank you, sorry, thank you, so much,
friends, your life will be successful if you
forward this video to three people and
tell all three of them, you will also tell yourself, like,
share and subscribe. It is
very important to subscribe because only one and a
half lakhs are left. We have 170 left to reach 1 million families.
Okay,
which celebrity do you want to see next on this
show? Write it in the comments below and
pray that he says yes.
[Music]